ADANMA O. OKWUCHI

Administrative Associate

CONTACT

36, Amusa Street, Agodo-Egbe, Ikotun, Lagos, Nigeria.

(234)-805-231-2357

okwuchiadanma@gmail.com

EDUCATION

Oduduwa University, Osun State—

BSc. Biochemistry

October 2015 - November 2019

TOOLS & SKILLS

- Tools:
 - Ms Suite
 - o Figma,
 - o Notion
- Skills:
 - o HTML, CSS & JavaScript
 - o Active listening,
 - Excellent Communication Skill,
 - Good reading comprehension,
 - Creative writing.

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Resourceful and experienced Administrative personnel offering expertise in customer service, travel coordination, and file management. Dedicated team member with high attention to detail and strong organizational skills. Capable of handling multiple projects simultaneously with a high degree of accuracy.

WORK HISTORY

Euphoria Labs, Lekki, Lagos —

Executive Assistant

August 2020 - Till date

- Conducted research to prepare, gather and proof briefing materials, agendas and decks for executive-level meetings.
- Produced accurate office files, updated spreadsheets, and crafted presentations to support executives and boost team efficiency.
- Created and maintained computer- and paper-based filing and organisation systems for records, reports and documents.

Longview Communications, Ejigbo, Lagos — *Secretary*

January 2020 - Till date

- Met incoming customers and provided friendly, knowledgeable help.
- Drafted and corrected professional business letters, internal memoranda and less formal email communication.
- Managed clerical needs of company employees, including copying, faxing and file management.

CLEDON Investment CO. LTD, Lagos Island,

Lagos — Personal Assistant January 2014 – September 2017

- Respond to mails and phone calls
- Collating and filing expenses.
- Typing, compiling and preparing reports